Damn cake...
How pathetic you look....
Iorogi.
Kobato.
How do I do this again?
The simplest things in life
end up being the most difficult.
I just want to smile when I'm happy
and sing a song whenever I please.
I was told, "Someday,
your dream will come true."
But when exactly will that be?
I can't wait that long!
I spread my arms
on the count of one two three
and gather all the light in the world.
Tell me,
isn't there something I can do?
Even if someone hurts my feelings,
I'll keep running toward the light.
Even if I trip, fall, and cry my eyes out, I still believe.
Although it may seem silly...
I believe in tomorrow.
Production
The Kobato Protection Group
...Silver Eyes.
It's Kobato!
Morning, Kobato!
Good morning!
Kobato! Can I tie a ribbon on him?
Him?
Oh, you mean Ioryogi?
Hey, come on now. Give me a break.
Yes, please do!
So cute!
Yes! I'm sure Ioryogi is pleased too!
Who's pleased?!
Good morning!
Good morning, Kobato.
We'll be counting on you today too.
Okay!
Then I'll be back later okay, Ioryogi?
I wonder why she carries that around.
I'm sure it's because it's something important.
Yum, yum!
The Bear's
Baumkuchen
Shop
Baumkuchen, bakey, bakey.
Ha, bakey, bakey!
The bear in the forest is baking...
Huh?
How annoying.
Hurry up and just get in. Ginsei.
He's not here, just to tell ya.
I know.
So then what're you here for?
I just wanted to know.
What that guy is thinking.
Why ask me? Hmph.
Whatever.
Even though we're in these forms now,
we're both inhabitants of the spirit world.
What's all this about now?
It's been like this since the beginning.
The heavenly world, the human world, the underworld, and the spirit world.
The only ones not conscious of the existence of these separate worlds
are the humans of the human world.
In the heavenly world resides the angels under God's control,
in the underworld, the demons under the Devil,
and in the spirit world, there's us under the King of Spirits.
In each of these worlds,
nonaggression is the fundamental rule.
And yet, that stupid Iorogi....
Hm?
Right, right, that slightly stupid Iorogi.
He tried to start a war with heaven and
what you're looking at is the result of that.
The reason Iorogi tried to start a war
with heaven in the first place was because
there was something there that he just had to have, no matter what.
But...
He wasn't able to get it.
Yeah. It would've been better if he had just tried to slip in quietly and steal it like the Devil's brat.
But in the end, it was our loss,
and for the crime of violating the ban on aggression, he was turned into a stuffed animal.
I became the bear of this
Bear's Baunkuchen Shop,
and Zuisho was changed into that strange looking bird.
I guess the almighty God
can lose his patience too.
We got dragged in, but as the ringleader, he got the worst end of the deal.
What does Iorogi have to do in order to be able to return to the spirit world?
Until that girl's wish is granted, Iorogi is stuck in that form and can't return to the spirit world.
Her wish?
When her bottle is filled with the healed
hearts of humans, her wish will come true.
His contract with God is to help her fulfill her wish.
I don't know what he's thinking either.
But what I can say is that ever since Iorogi came to the human world...
No, he's changed ever since he started living with that girl.
Just leave him be for a while, why don't you?
Why don't you have a taste of—
Eh?
Jeez.
And it's so delicious too.
If any of my friends from before saw me like this, they'd cry!
Oh?
You can't catch me!
Good morning, Kobato.
Domoto!
Why did you come to the Nursery?
I just had to see Kiyokazu about something.
Guys, it's time for lunch!
Wash your hands and go inside.
Okay!
Kiyokazu.
Why are you here?
I thought it would be a good idea for you to come to today's seminar so I came by to get you.
I'm not going.
And I came here with my hopes up.
A semi what...?
A seminar. For college.
Oh, it's for college?
Yup.
You didn't go last time, did you?
I think it'd be a good idea for you to show up this time.
Please go, Fujimoto!
Can't. I'm busy.
Fujimoto!
Kobato! Don't worry, I have an idea.
That's enough for today.
You have an important seminar to attend this afternoon, don't you?
Miss Sayaka...
I've come here many times to help out too.
That's when I noticed it.
In the afternoon, the kids have nap time,
and Kobato will still be around to help out.
We'll be fine.
But...
Fujimoto, you're always such a big help.
But I would really like it if you actually went to college.
Please.
All right.
He's so obedient!
He's only obedient for Miss Sayaka.
I can't deal with this piece of crap anymore!
See you, Kobato.
I'll be back some other time.
Yes, please come visit again!
Bye for now!
Have a safe trip!
I'll try my best to do Fujimoto's work!
Wow, that's great!
I can't get it off! Damn that
Fujimoto for tying it so tightly!
Thank you so much for today, Kobato. You being here was really a huge help!
I wasn't really—
Go home and get a good rest, okay?
Okay!
That ribbon looks good on little Ioryogi, doesn't it?
Little... Ioryogi...?
Yes!
See you tomorrow!
It's still kind of hot out, isn't it?
The earthy places are cool though.
Oh, that feels nice.
Doesn't it, Ioryogi?
Huh?
What do you think you're doing?
Your head was all scrunched up right here, Ioryogi!
Do you know why?
Is it because you're hungry?
Kobato.
The seasons are changing, one after another.
You didn't come here to help out at the Nursery, did you?
But today, Fujimoto wasn't here and I wanted to make up for his share of the work as well.
That's just it.
You should be doing what you came here to do!
If you don't hurry up and fill up this bottle,
your wish won't be able to come true anymore.
Ginsei!
A friend of yours, Ioryogi?
Ioryogi!
It's her, isn't it.
Kobato!
Ioryogi...
Hm? Isn't that...
You ass.
If that breaks, money can't buy another one!
Why?
Why do you plan on staying in that form here in the human world for so long?
I have something I need to do.
Master Genko!
Zuisho! Don't be flapping around inside!
You'll get feathers in the batter!
I can't help it. I'm a bird right now.
I know, I know.
So, what is it?
Oh, right!
That violent and selfish guy who is
stuck in the form of a stuffed animal
and the reckless one who was here earlier
are now locked together in what
seems to be an explosive situation!
Is that so.
That's all you have to say?
Then take this and give it to the loser as a get-well present.
Can we really leave them be?
Those two spell big trouble!
No one would be able to get between them.
Iorogi was the one who took in Ginsei in the first place.
Iorogi even named him.
His eyes are silver and he's a
silver being. That's why he's Ginsei.
No matter what happens, that's their relationship.
I did try to stop them, but it
just devolved into a fist fight.
I'll bet.
He was picked up and named by Iorogi; it's no wonder that he continues to obsess over him.
There's no choice but to let them resolve it themselves.
Give back the bottle.
Come and get it yourself, Ioryogi.
Watch it, I'll burn you where you lay.
There's no way you could hold me down in that form.
Why you—!
Pathetic, aren't you.
In shape and in name.
What the hell's this "Ioryogi" nonsense?
I-o...ryo?
I-o-ro-gi.
I-o-ryo-gi?
I-o-ro-gi, dammit!
Wrong! Ioryogi!
Got it, Ioryogi!
I've become fond of having my name pronounced like that.
Just give back the bottle already.
Say that you'll return to the spirit world.
I told you I have something I need to do, didn't I?
I'm not going back, at least not until I see this through.
That... wish thing, right?
What is it about that girl?
She's...
...put me through some terrible things.
Then just get rid of her.
What did you say?
If that girl wasn't here, you wouldn't have to worry about wishes or any of that.
You should also be able to return to the spirit world.
The you of the past would have done so.
Probably would've.
That girl's clumsy and knows nothing of charm...
I'll do my best!
...and always puts others before
herself to the point of exhaustion,
even though they never asked her to.
But you know...
That doesn't make me hate her.
I can't listen to this anymore.
Darn you, my stuffing's coming out here!
If she doesn't fill up this bottle,
her wish won't be able to come true...
Ginsei!
Then if there's no bottle...
Stop!
I have no intention of listening to you when you're like that!
Ginsei!
Please!
Please give back the bottle.
Without that, Kobato...
I'm begging you.
He's changed ever since he
started living with that girl.
"I'm begging you"?
You never would've said
something like that in the past.
Hurry up and fulfill your goal.
Ginsei...
Ioryogi!
Kobato?
Kohaku!
What's the matter?
Ioryogi's disappeared!
Ioryogi? He was in Sakura Park...
Come, catch me if you can!
Oh, you!
It seemed like he was having fun playing tag with a friend from the spirit world,
so I didn't call out to him.
At Sakura Park you said?
Thank you so much!
You're welcome!
Damn this inconvenient body!
But if I can make it this far—
That hurts, you idiot!
Ioryogi!
Ioryogi! Where are you?
Hey!
Fujimoto!
Here.
Ioryogi!
Thank goodness, Ioryogi!
Thank you so much for finding Ioryogi!
Ioryogi got lost and...
Got lost?
I'm so, so glad he's all right!
Is that thing really important?
Yes! Ioryogi and I have always been together!
Yummy.
That bear—how thoughtful.
It looks really good on you!
You!
Ioryogi.
Thank you for bringing back this bottle for me.
I'm so grateful!
Dobato!
Minus 200 points!
What were you doing?! Why did you let your bottle get stolen like that?!
I'm sorry...
Is today some sort of dress up day?!
All of you have been tying this thing on me!
Ioryogi and I have always been together!
Ioryogi?
What?
The ribbon does look nice on you, doesn't it?
Not at all!
Of course it does!
Look, if we tie one more, it'll be even—
Hey, stop that!
And then if we tie another one on top of that...
Hey, I said stop!!
Let's tie just one more!
Sto-mmph!
Even though we all want to fly,
we're being deceived by gravity.
In reality, everybody can already fly.
The reason why that child looks so sad
might be because she left her shadow somewhere.
If so...
If telling you "Thank you",
or hearing "Thank you" just makes you smile,
then doing those things will make me happy.
And they'll make you happy too.
Don't worry, we're together.
It's mysterious as to why tears roll down
even though I'm happy.
Next
...The Angel and the Protected Person.